worldoftrucks.com 2017-08-05

# World of Trucks | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SCS Software s.r.o. (also furthermore referred as "we" and/or "us") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://www.worldoftrucks.com](http://www.worldoftrucks.com/) website ("Site").

This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in privacy laws and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a specific person, or to identify an individual in context. 

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address, name and/or Nickname. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" in order to: a) enhance User experience, b) understand and save User's preferences for future visits and c) keep track of advertisements. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. (please note each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If User disables cookies off, some features may be disabled and it also may turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of Site services may not function properly.

Please note that we, along with third-party vendors, such as Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

## How we use collected information

We may use the information which collects from you when Users register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways and purposes:

  * To personalize user experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.   
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve customer service   
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To improve our Site in order to better serve you.   
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature.   
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails regarding products and services.   
We may use the email address to respond also to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

## How we protect your information

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information / Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

We may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Electronic newsletters

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licencors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Changes to this privacy policy

SCS Software s.r.o. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us via [support@scssoft.com](mailto:support@scssoft.com?subject=Question%20about%20the%20World%20of%20Trucks%20Privacy%20Policy) or via registered mail on:

SCS Software s.r.o.   
I.P.Pavlova 5   
120 00 Praha 2   
Czech Republic 

**This document was last updated on April 20, 2015**
